Dario Maroto

Madrid, Community of Madrid, Spain



dmarotolopez@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/dario-maroto

Summary

Currently I'm delighted of being part of a course to adquire new lifetime tools, upgrade my skills and change my career.

Daily learning and using in personal projects tools and languages like HTML 5, CSS 3, JavaScript 6, PHP 8, SQL 8, Bootstrap 5.3 and much more to come.

A hard working individual with more than 10 years of experience in customer care and customer support which give me impressive communicative and interpersonal capacities developed across my work as a shop assistant and Taxi driver.

Great attention to detail and quick learning of new tasks as proven as a Kitchen assistant and in my daily work at Accenture as a Content moderator.

Skills for multitasking, teamwork and working in very demanding conditions as proven through my chores as a Kitchen assistant, Content moderation and Shop assistant.

Always looking to grow personally and professionally, and for new challenges and goals as proven all my lifetime going to different countries, like Portugal or England, searching to enrich and strengthen my experience and my background as a worker.

Experience



Content Analyst, Data Entry and User Accounts Support

Accenture

Mar 2020 - Feb 2023 (3 years)

As a content moderator I watch and review content generated by users, and take action over this content to maintain internet a little more safer.

I also help users to regain and recover access to lost, stolen or hacked accounts in a friendly, correct and timely manner.



Kitchen Assistant

The Stuyck Co. Madrid

Sep 2018 - Oct 2019 (1 year 2 months)

Mise en place; cleaning, cutting and measuring ingredients, different kinds of vegetables, meat, fishes, etc; production of different kinds of sauces and broths in order to use them in the recipes.

Preparation of different dishes and recipesand handling a grill and a deep fryer.

Cleaning the kitchen at the end of the service.



Kitchen Assistant

Restaurante Rochacho

Dec 2017 - Sep 2018 (10 months)

Mise en place; cleaning, cutting and measuring ingredients, different kinds of vegetables, meat, fishes, etc; production of different kinds of sauces and broths in order to use them in the recipes.

Preparation of different dishes, recipes and handling a grill and a deep fryer.

■ Kitchen Assistant

Jan 2017 - Aug 2017 (8 months)

Mise en place; cleaning, cutting and measuring ingredients, different kinds of vegetables, meat, fishes, etc; production of different kinds of sauces and broths in order to use them in the recipes.

Preparation of different dishes and recipesand handling a grill and a deep fryer.

Cleaning the kitchen at the end of the service.

Shop Assistant

Greengrocery

Aug 2012 - Dec 2016 (4 years 5 months)

Four years committed to customer services in a grocery store, giving personal attention and making customers daily shopping experience enjoyable.

Doing cashier roles, closing the register at the end of the day, loading and unloading of bags of vegetables, delivery services and cleaning the premises.

Taxi driver

Taxi

Jan 2008 - Jun 2012 (4 years 6 months)

Four years driving through the streets of Madrid, working again in a function related to customer service.

My daily job was to drive from one point to another in the city, making the journey as safe and enjoyable as possible for users.

Shop Assistant

greengrocery

Aug 2003 - Dec 2008 (5 years 5 months)

Four years committed to customer services in a grocery store, giving personal attention and making customers daily shopping experience enjoyable.

Doing cashier roles, closing the register at the end of the day, loading and unloading of bags of vegetables, delivery services and cleaning the premises.

Education

CDM Embajadores

Certificado de profesionalidad , Programación informática, aplicaciones específicas May 2023 - Oct 2023

Licenses & Certifications

Learn Python 3 Course - Codecademy

Skills

Full-Stack Development • Software Development • Databases • PHP • SQL • Back end • Desarrollo front end • Bases de datos • JavaScript • HTML